it's footsteps i can't believe it someone really is grilling meat i sincerely hope it's not
criminals who got stuck in this place we've just set up camp we're not looking for a fight here
i know that voice wait a sec is that you laos namori friends of yours former party long time no see
well i guess it's only been a week oh and by the way these are my current employers the tonsus
i guess their scholars somebody else hired and they pay real well and those two are kaka and kiki
though don't ask me who is who
namari how how could you abandon falon like that abandon i wasn't gonna risk my life for free
there was no point why you
marcil you need to rest hey uh don't push yourself if you kicked the bucket falon would be sad
oh yeah is there a healer in your group we'd like to request their assistance what's your offer
some healthy meat hell no
come namari show charity the dungeon and you'll be bled dry
honestly even that corpse we found on the way had a revival fee ready
there's an undine up ahead so maybe you should stay here is there now i see you all went and
angered did you huh we'll be just fine gnomes you see have lived amongst the spirits since ancient times
and because of that long history we're like kin so there is nothing to be afraid of
undine
oh magnificent water spirits i beseech thee to answer my call
oh that's bad
you were correct
no namari
how could you let this happen
she'll be all right
you're off a rain brettie rain brettie go
you old bastard always using me as a freaking meat shield
of course that's why i pay you so much
revival magic huh
it's the one type of magic i hate the most
what is it you hate so much about it
watching it leaves a pit in my belly
the dead shouldn't come back to life
that's true outside the dungeon
but it's a normal thing in here
that ain't normal
ain't nothing normal about it
no the boy's right
this entire dungeon is affected by a very powerful spell
it shackles people's souls to their bodies
therefore no matter how grave the wound your soul will not depart
and simply healing the injury will revive you
the way i see it is it's not that the dead are coming back to life
it's that death itself is forbidden inside this place
it is truly a dreadful curse indeed
fascinating isn't it
this is just the type of ancient sorcery that i research
i came to examine some magic circles nearby
but my guard is unreliable
if you agree to assist me
i will heal your friend in return
it's a deal then
senshi and i will accompany you
it's around here
elf writing huh
so ugly and difficult to read
remove the roots
they're in the way
seriously
you've got to stop with the creepy ass swords
lios
i've told you countless times
i should only use store-bought ones
yeah i know
make sure that it's dwarf made too
don't do business with shops manned by a half foot
and don't swing your sheath
as for you
that axe
you need to take better care of it
it looks horrible
i should probably chill huh
nah
when it comes to handling weapons
there's no one i trust more than you
stay back
what is it
there's a monster
well defeat it then
i don't know what or where it is though
what
then how are you certain something is there
i just do
you must be joking
sir
when lios starts acting like this
i think we should trust him
i will not indulge baseless hunches
if it's hiding we'll just drag it out
oh i see now
i never would have guessed ten of us
this isn't the time to analyze them
kiki
are you all right
what are you two doing
hurry up and kill that thing
our weapons aren't gonna reach that
go
just save her
what if we got caught on purpose to get closer to it
tentacles are cnidarian creatures
upon touching skin
poisonous barbs will release and paralyze
if you get captured
there's a high chance you won't make it out alive
i will revive you if that happens
shut the hell up
fine
i'm going in
senshi
can i borrow your helmet
it's too dangerous
don't do this
you can't put all of your trust into revival magic
i'm not
the thing i'm putting my trust into here
is you and senshi
what's that mean
reach me
all right
hey danger noodles
i guess it still stings through armor huh
i'm already losing feeling in my arm
even so
what are you doing up there
aim for its torso you idiot
damn it
so that's what he meant
yeah sure
give me the toughest job
lios
you doing okay
sure it doesn't look like it
huh
wait
what happened
oh kiki
you poor thing
hang on
i'm going to heal you now
hmm
this is a tough one
i'm afraid this will take some time
yeah
that's fine
what the hell happened to your face
i got stung by tentacles
what should i do with this
why are you still holding it
it paralyzed my hand when i ripped it off
and now it's stuck
your hand looks like a gnome's in that state
let's see
so it's an ivy tentacle
rinsing with vinegar
helps subdue the nidocyte's barbs
although depending on the species
it could have the opposite effect
so be careful
cut an x into the exposed surface
then peel downward
to remove the outer skin of the nidocyte
apparently it's tasty
are you making a joke
no that was a little piece of trivia about it
if that's the only way i guess there's no other choice
this really isn't bad at all
but it'll be better once cooked properly
let me have a taste too
interesting
i think the taste differs in each spot
you must be imagining that
i'm not
i swear
try it yourself
i just taste vinegar
you want to try myself
huh
try what
it's sour
and why is it kind of sticky
is it tarry
it's your turn tomorrow
try some from this spot right here
no i'm fine
really
we're plenty stocked on food
so i'll pass
but it tastes good
it doesn't
but it could once it's cooked
maybe we should smash it and fry it
hell yeah
success
all right lios
it's your turn
fantastic
though
could you start with her first
being healthy really is the best feeling
you healed me
thank you so much
and you too li-
what is wrong with your face
don't forget to thank namari
huh
that was quite a shot you made
to think you took the thing down
with a single arrow
we would have been boned
if you weren't so good
at using crossbows
actually
it was my first time touching one
what
namari
hmm
the whole fallon thing aside
you did help us out
so thank you for that
of course it was my pleasure
getting a job done's easy
when you've got an incentive
like money involved
hey come on you two
all of that's in the past now
like hell it is
you know this is kind of your problem too
so why are you acting like it isn't
huh
way to go lios
that's not what i meant
here there leader
seems unpleasant
it's watching us
do you think it's still upset
i don't know how you angered it so much in the first place
yeah the way it attacked me was so brutal
i may have poured a whole pot of boiling water on it
ah so that's how
as expected from an elf
always causing trouble
anyone could have made that mistake
is there any way to calm it down without magic
we have to get through here
of course there is
an undine is a grouping of tiny spirits
once each of those individual spirits die
the next generation is born with a clean slate
from what i remember
a spirit's lifespan is about one week
a whole week huh
we can't wait that long
i agree
and that is why we'll be returning to the surface for now
we will continue our research later
yarn
prepare the returning spell
hey lios come here
this is our chance don't you think
mr tansu
i have a favor
you want me to return to the surface too
but why now
i don't get it
look your mana's currently depleted
and i hear that's like having anemia for magic users
so you should go back with mr tansu
i'm fine though
it's hard to believe how good i feel
it was probably the liver
nutrients don't show up in the body that fast
they slowly build up
yeah that's great
anyway i feel much better than before
a nap was just the thing to restore my mana
if that's the case how come there's no mana running through your staff like usual
oh this hang on
let's go
what are you laughing at
sorry
just never seen that look on your face before
hey uh
what are the rest of you gonna do
you can't fight a dragon with only three people
i won't be doing any fighting
and let's not forget that axe of yours
that thing won't even make so much as a scratch on the dragon
namari you've defeated lots of dragons before
that right
sure have
then
can you
please namari
can you rejoin the party
what's all this
work together with laos
and defeat the red dragon
no matter the cost
we need to save fallon
just this once
i'll get the money to pay you somehow
stop it marsil
but why
the adventurer circle's tight-knit
so rumors spread around faster than you can blink
in fact i bet you heard that namari was struggling with money
isn't that right
mr tonsil
yes
so if she rejoins her former party to make a quick buck
she'll gain a reputation as someone who will do anything you ask her to if you pay her enough
i don't think it'll prevent her from getting jobs but
the type of clients she'll get will change
it's best for everyone
if you give up on trying to get her to return
you heard the man marsil
you should go back too
no
i can recover my mana
and i'm going to use the undine to do it
huh
how so
i'll catch it and
drink it
wait
really
what's with that reaction
where's your usual enthusiasm
i don't have much interest in spirits
okay but they eat mana to live
so i have no doubt they're completely filled with this stuff
catching it is probably going to be harder than killing it
let's see
water spirits are weak to heat
so if we take advantage of that
maybe we could attack it with a heated sword
or we could spill some oil
and corner it on the fiery lake
then after we attack it and it splatters onto the floor
i'll slurp it all up
wouldn't it punch holes in your body from the inside
yeah you're right
there must be a way
just think
if we heat this pan and use it as a shield then we can attack and defend
that spirit destroyed stone pillars
what's a shoddy pan gonna do
how dare you call it shoddy
this is a family heirloom that's been very well taken care of for multiple generations
it never burns and evenly distributes heat
it's the perfect pan
whoa wait a sec
this color
this shine
this weight
this feel
it's adamantine isn't it
unbelievable
as a weapon this can smash through dragon bones
as armor it can block a dragon's fangs
adamantine is what blacksmiths dream about
why was it turned into a pan
it started as a shield but it was useless to me like that
are you kidding me that's such a waste
can it hold up against an undine
of course it can
since we have both a pan and a lid
two of us can take one
trap the undine inside
and then put it over a fire and kill it
that's the only way
even if the shield is sturdy the undine might be too powerful
that dwarf might be fine
but will lios be able to hold it down
when the surface warps raise the pan
try not to spill anything
heads up
it's so powerful
lios
namori
no
all right
that's it
we got this
on the fire
now
yes you did it
amazing truly barbaric strength
namari
thank you so much
you too lios
are you okay
their stature would make you think otherwise
but tall men are actually weak
oh yeah
you don't have to chug it that fast
i want to make sure i absorb the spirit's mana
don't you know
eating foods that help with absorption is the basics of nutrition
so does that
so does that mean
let's get cooking
potatoes carrots onions
peel the skin from the tentacles
and roughly chop them
salt and pepper the kelpie meat
put the meat in a pan
and when it's browned
add in the onions and carrots and fry them
add that to the undine
make sure to skim off the scum
then add potatoes and herbs
and let it simmer
it's ready
huh
where'd they go
they went on over to the other tower to examine it
we're back
who knew there would be so many of them
i'm glad we managed to clear them out
um
hey
would you
like to eat with us
here you go
looks delish
did you make it marcelle
yeah but i had sent you around to help me out
here you go nomari
don't worry about serving it
hurry up and eat
oh
right
it's working
a little bit of my mana came back
so
you've been cooking monsters you find here this whole time
yeah pretty much
i was prepared to get criticized for leaving the party but
i never thought i'd have to see them in this kind of situation
this must be some form of punishment
yum
everything's so rich
how is this possible in such a short time
is it the pan
is adamantine good for cooking
hey your name's senshi yeah
i uh apologize
for insulting your axe
it's fine
i got no interest in fortune so it's not like i'm gonna fix it
some old buddies i had would always get on my case for not being able to tell the difference between oars
nomari
we will be returning to the surface
you're free to stay here if you want to
wait seriously
you've got to at least stay to try this
the texture is kind of weird but it's still pretty good
uh
i can't really ask you to trust me
this isn't about money for me
i really want to become a member of your party
i promise to do my best
you know chill chuck
i'm surprised
i thought you'd be the first to leave the group for sure
i didn't see you as the type
to take on an unpaid job
well yeah i only take jobs that pay me up front
though it gets kind of tricky
since i can't leave when i wanna
huh you're only here because it's a job
it's not because of friendship or anything
listen marcel
here's something you should know
anybody who tells you they don't need a reward
are honestly the people you should trust the least
oh by the way
what's shuru up to
don't know seemed like he had some other plans cooked up
he was so in love with fallon he wanted to propose
so i'm willing to bet he's looking for her
huh seriously
so dense
yep
all right everyone
i know fallon's special to you
but i hope you make it back okay
huh
same to you namari
see ya
Thank you.